<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Tips &amp; Tricks | My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/categories/tips-amp-tricks/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-17T11:51:51-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To: Eliminate the On Behalf Of Message]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/06/27/how-to-eliminate-the-on-behalf-of-message/"/>
    <updated>2011-06-27T09:56:46-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/06/27/how-to-eliminate-the-on-behalf-of-message</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When you check your messages in some readers, are they showing up as "Sent by You, on Behalf of SendGrid"? Or does it look even messier than that? Well, it's really quite an easy fix!</p>

<p>Some ISPs or mail readers, such as Hotmail or Outlook, will display a message with the Sender header set as “on behalf of” and then the address that is in the Sender header. This is caused by the <strong>DomainKeys</strong> configuration of your account.</p>

<p>By default, SendGrid signs all e-mail with DomainKeys to improve deliverability with some smaller domains. However, with accounts that do not have whitelabeling, this means that the domain in the From field will not have the proper DNS record to authenticate the e-mail. Because of this, SendGrid inserts a Sender header, and the e-mail can then be properly authenticated.</p>

<p>However, the vast majority of recipient servers now check authenticity using DKIM, which is the evolution of Domain Keys. All emails sent out by SendGrid are signed with DKIM, whether your account is whitelabeled or not. So if you're having this problem, feel free to disable DomainKeys, and it should not have any impact on your deliverability. You can disable them by going to your Apps, <a href="http://sendgrid.com/app">here</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPF Records:  Don't have more than 10 DNS lookups!]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/06/27/spf-records-dont-have-more-than-10-dns-lookups/"/>
    <updated>2011-06-27T09:44:01-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/06/27/spf-records-dont-have-more-than-10-dns-lookups</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Sender Policy Framework (SPF) specification has a limit of 10 on the number of DNS lookups required to fully resolve an SPF record. This limit is in place to prevent SPF lookups from being a useful avenue for Denial of Service attacks. However, it is possible to quickly exceed this limit through the reckless use of the <strong>include</strong> modifier.</p>

<p>Section <a href="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc4408#section-10.1">10.1</a> of the SPF RFC, "Processing Limits", specifies the following in regards to DNS lookups:</p>

<p><em>SPF implementations MUST limit the number of mechanisms and modifiers that do DNS lookups to at most 10 per SPF check, including any lookups caused by the use of the "include" mechanism or the "redirect" modifier.  If this number is exceeded during a check, a PermError MUST be returned.  The "include", "a", "mx", "ptr", and "exists" mechanisms as well as the "redirect" modifier do count against this limit.  The "all", "ip4", and "ip6" mechanisms do not require DNS lookups and therefore do not count against this limit. The "exp" modifier does not count against this limit because the DNS lookup to fetch the explanation string occurs after the SPF record has been evaluated.</em></p>

<p>Is your SPF record validating?  You might want to find out here: <a href="http://www.kitterman.com/spf/validate.html">SPF Record Testing Tools</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
