<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Apps | My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/categories/apps/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-17T11:51:51-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I send from multiple FROM addresses or different domains?]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/05/24/can-i-send-from-multiple-from-addresses-or-different-domains/"/>
    <updated>2011-05-24T11:15:57-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/05/24/can-i-send-from-multiple-from-addresses-or-different-domains</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yes, it is OK to send email from different FROM addresses.</p>

<p>Be aware that you will want to turn off Domain Keys if you are sending from domains different from the domain provisioned with SendGrid as the foreign domains will cause Domain Keys to fail.</p>

<p>To fix this, you can add a Sender header, however this will cause an 'on behalf of' message to be shown in some mail readers. More information about Domain Keys and SendGrid can be found <a href="/documentation/apps/domain-keys/">here.</a></p>

<p>Alternatively you can use the <a href="/documentation/api/smtp-api/">SMTP API</a> to override the domain in the Domain Keys filter. The <a href="/documentation/api/smtp-api/developers-guide/">Developer's Guide</a> is a page that describes the "filters" that can be specified in the X-SMTPAPI header, this allows you to enable or disable Apps for the purpose of the SMTP API transaction.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To: Import CSV files to the Newsletter App]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/05/13/how-to-import-csv-files-to-the-newsletter-app/"/>
    <updated>2011-05-13T07:38:47-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/blog/2011/05/13/how-to-import-csv-files-to-the-newsletter-app</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, you've got a CSV, Excel Spreadsheet, or other list of your users that you'd like to send your newsletter to, but you're not sure how to get that into our web-based Newsletter App? Here you go!</p>

<h2>Step 1: "Create New" Email List</h2>

<p>Once you're logged in, you go to the "Apps" tab, then select "My Newsletters" from the list on the right hand side of the page. That brings you to the Newsletter Dashboard. You then select "Create New" under the Recipient List:</p>

<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/csv1.png"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/csv1.png" alt="My Recipient Lists: Create New" /></a></p>

<h2>Step 2: Name your new List</h2>

<p>Name your list something definitive. Is this your list of blog followers, or only the people who've purchased exclusive content Maybe it's all the clients who attended your seminar last week, and you want to let them know about the next series. "Blog Readers", "eBook Purchaser", "May 12 Seminar Attendees", you get the idea.</p>

<h2>Step 3: Upload CSV</h2>

<p>If it's not already selected, select the "Upload List" radio button, then click the "Upload CSV" button. Once the file is uploaded, you may need to drag &amp; drop the "Name" and "Email" cells to make sure they are over the appropriate columns. The column headers are not required in the CSV file. After the upload process, You will get to preview the file. There, you will fill in or drag &amp; drop the column headers. The order of the columns doesn't matter, but there must be an email column. Once everything's lined up right, it should look something like this:</p>

<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/csv31.png"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/csv31.png" alt="Example of Uploaded CSV" /></a></p>

<h2>Step 4: Review &amp; Verify List</h2>

<p>Here, you can make sure that all data was imported properly, delete line items that are incorrect. Once you are done here, select "Verify". That's it, you're ready to create a newsletter, and send it to that list!</p>

<h2>What CSV formats do we accept?</h2>

<p>Basically, anything that would reasonably be considered a CSV file. Below are some examples of what would be ok:</p>

<h3>Example 1: No Header</h3>

<p>Alice Alderaan,alice@gmail.com
"Bob Beauford","bob@live.com"
Cindy Carson,cindy@yahoo.com
David Donald,"david@hotmail.com"
"Erica Elvis",erica@anonymous.org</p>

<h3>Example 2: Headers Included</h3>

<p>name,email
Alice Alderaan,alice@gmail.com
"Bob Beauford","bob@live.com"
Cindy Carson,cindy@yahoo.com
David Donald,"david@hotmail.com"
"Erica Elvis",erica@anonymous.org</p>

<h3>Example 3: Acceptable Headers</h3>

<ul>
<li><p>"name",email,</p></li>
<li><p>name,"email"</p></li>
<li><p>"name","email"</p></li>
<li><p>name,email</p></li>
<li><p>email,address,"name"</p></li>
<li><p>userid,"email",address</p></li>
</ul>


<h2>Well, we hope you have found this a helpful article in our "How To" series. Happy importing!</h2>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
